[
Music]
Hello friends, welcome to Option Gyan channel.
Friends, today we are going to discuss this
topic, its name is Business Industry.
You have to click on this account.
I will give you a
one-handed option
and if the price of the option is
around
₹500, friends, it will be given
at different rates, so you should buy
it at a marketable lifetime, so it is
possible that if a correction comes, it will happen, so it can happen
that you
took this option today and tomorrow it starts to fall, that is, a
correction comes in the market, then
you will feel that what has happened, then
you should not panic at that time, you will
know the level where to go and invest
and if you do Everest, then your
nutritional value decreases, so
if the stock hits a big price from there, then
your portfolio becomes green very quickly, so
next think, have you
bought any stock
whose quantity will be ₹10, then
buy its quantity yourself  If that
stock reaches ₹50,
then you will get two point bikes there,
approximately
12 quantities, for ₹100, whose
total will be for the targets of three friends
and the positive is that you have your A, that is,
one which will be yours,
whose cost will be around Shyam,
so if the stock goes from here from ₹50 again
towards A Super
and goes a little further, then
you will make a profit of 30%
in the dog, so
now to avoid people from getting nervous, I will
take different level plugs so that you
people will be able to understand these things, where to
wait, and friends, as I do not give this, there is some
support area, so
from there the stock will move very high for four to five
times, if you people have seen all my old
videos, then you people will know that at the
level which I give, it becomes
very difficult for the stock to break like this
and the stock washes back from there,
so friends, these levels are very
important, you people should keep a note with you.  Keep it done
and secondly let's discuss one more thing that
what you have to do in the stock, that
right now you have to invest only 20%, that
on the 68th of the daily you have to invest 30%, that
chart is done then,
similarly we do the chart in the group for
21 minutes ago, okay, so what
you have to do here, you have to
invest 30% of your capital,
that 30% of your capital will be invested on the 68th, the
remaining 40% of your capital friends will be invested
16 times and the remaining 30
% of
your capital will be invested around ₹500, right, so
this is how you have to invest,
friends, if you understand
where to invest in the stock and from where to
exit, then you will
get the benefit of things in the long term,
friends, sometimes you may feel
that this secret is far away, but
look, I am asking you to invest 100% of your capital, it is
not that if you do it in this
way  If you do this at different rates then your profit will
not be much and if the stock is
all this and trans friends whenever there is a stock of MS Word that
breaks out then it
gives breakfast in these houses or if it goes to its second
level then from
there when it hits Bigg Boss back
then you people will get to see a very good profit
if you people are watching my old videos
then you people must be able to understand everything
I hope friends you must have
liked my video
and it will be very beneficial for you
with this hope friends I end this video
thank you
friends if you like this video then
please do not forget to like share and subscribe
thank you for watching my video